Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXII is arranged in 33 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXII. 1931 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 398-0. 1931 Convention
    - General. Proceedings, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 4-8)
      May 11-18, 1931.
    - General, 1929 (Box 533, Folder 9)
    - General. Report of Committee on Legislation, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 10-12)
      1931 May 11
    - General. Pictures and Charts, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 13)
    - General. Roster, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 14)
    - General. Newspaper Clippings, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 398-1. 1931 Convention
    - Convention City, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 16)
    - Convention City, 1929 (Box 533, Folder 17)
    - Convention City, 1928 (Box 533, Folder 18)
    - Convention City, 1927 (Box 533, Folder 19)
    - Convention City, 1926 (Box 533, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 398-2. 1931 Convention
    - Convention Book, 1928-1931 (Box 533, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 398-3. 1931 Convention
    - Convention Committee, 1929 (Box 533, Folder 22)
    - Convention Committee, 1928 (Box 533, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 398-4. 1931 Convention
    - Convention Hall, 1928 (Box 533, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 398-5. 1931 Convention
    - Hotel Accommodations, 1930 (Box 533, Folder 25)
    - Hotel Accommodations, 1928-1929 (Box 533, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 398-6. 1931 Convention
    - Insurance Committee, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 27)
    - Insurance Committee, 1928 (Box 533, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 398-7. 1931 Convention
    - Committee on Laws, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 29)
    - Committee on Laws, 1929 (Box 533, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 398-8. 1931 Convention
    - Convention Reporter, 1930 (Box 533, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 398-9. 1931 Convention
    - Convention Committee Bills, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 398-10. 1931 Convention
    - Guards, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 398-11. 1931 Convention
    - Election of Delegates, 1930-1931 (Box 533, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 398-12. 1931 Convention
    - Convention Call, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 398-13. 1931 Convention
    - Pullman Rates, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 36-37)
  - Sub-Series 398-14. 1931 Convention
    - Reports, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 398-15. 1931 Convention
    - Reduced Railroad Fares, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 398-16. 1931 Convention
    - Special Trains, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 398-17. 1931 Convention
    - Grand Sergeant-at-Arms, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 398-18. 1931 Convention
    - Application for Appointments, 1931 (Box 533, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 398-19. 1931 Convention
    - Committee on Financial Assistance, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 398-20. 1931 Convention
    - Ballots and Circulars, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 398-21. 1931 Convention
    - Proposed Amendments to Grand Lodge Laws, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 398-22. 1931 Convention
    - Transportation for Delegates, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 398-23. 1931 Convention
    - Resolutions, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 398-24. 1931 Convention
    - Speakers, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 398-25. 1931 Convention
    - Committee on Rules, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 398-26. 1931 Convention
    - Committee on Credentials, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 398-27. 1931 Convention
    - Board of Tellers, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 398-28. 1931 Convention
    - Grand Chaplain and Official Reader, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 398-29. 1931 Convention
    - Employees Attending, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 398-31. 1931 Convention
    - Refund of Railroad Fares, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 398-32. 1931 Convention
    - Destruction of Ballots, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 398-33. 1931 Convention
    - Official Minutes, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 14)